<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<deployment name="TelemetryDemo" divider="563" width="574" height="824" zoom="1.0" scroll-x="0" scroll-y="0" expand-description="true">
  <description>
    <![CDATA[This is a demo application that provides the basic framework for 
collecting data on a remote SPOT and passing it over the radio to 
a host application that can record and display it. It was written 
with the hope that it could be easily modified by people developing 
new SPOT applications.

Please see the README.txt file for more details.

To run in the Emulator just click on the "Deploy & Run All" button 
below. This will start up both the SPOT & host applications, which
will connect to each other in a few seconds. Click the "Collect Data" 
button to start plotting accelerometer readings from the SPOT.

In the main Solarium window right click on the virtual SPOT, choose 
"Display sensor panel" to open up a multi-tabbed panel that allows 
you to manipulate various sensor readings experienced by the
virtual SPOT. Select the tab marked "Accel".

As you change the acceleration values by moving the X, Y, and Z 
sliders in the "accel" tab of the sensor panel, you'll see a 
dynamically updated plot of the accelerometer readings along all 
three axis (X in green, Y in blue, Z in red and the total acceleration 
in orange).]]>
  </description>
  <spots>
    <role name="Report accelerometer readings" show-role="true" expand-description="false">
      <project file="Telemetry-onSpot/build.xml"/>
      <description>
        <![CDATA[The SPOT application consists of two Java classes: one to handle the
radio connection to the host application, and the second to read the
accelerometer and send the data to the host application.]]>
      </description>
    <spot address="VirtualSPOT" collapsed="false" show-status="true">
        <map-position x="200" y="300"/>
        <location value="in emulator"/>
      </spot>
    </role>
  </spots>
  <host-apps>
    <host-app  name="TelemetryDemo" collapsed="false">
      <role name="Display telemetry data" show-role="true" expand-description="false">
        <project file="Telemetry-onDesktop/build.xml"/>
        <description>
          <![CDATA[The host application consists of three main Java classes: one to
handle the radio connection to the remote SPOT, one to display the
data collected, and the third to manage the GUI.]]>
        </description>
      </role>
      <map-position x="200" y="300"/>
      <command name="ant host-run"/>
    </host-app>
  </host-apps>
</deployment>
